{
  "title": "Accessibility",
  "icon": "./assets/images/icon-accessibility.svg",
  "challenges": [
    {
      "question": "What does 'WCAG' stand for?",
      "answer": "Web Content Accessibility Guidelines",
      "badAnswers": [
        "Web Compliance Accessibility Guide",
        "Web Content Accessibility Goals",
        "Website Compliance and Accessibility Guidelines"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which element is used to provide alternative text for images for screen reader users?",
      "answer": "<img alt='description'>",
      "badAnswers": ["<alt>", "<figcaption>", "<description>"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What does ARIA stand for in web development?",
      "answer": "Accessible Rich Internet Applications",
      "badAnswers": [
        "Advanced Responsive Internet Assistance",
        "Accessible Responsive Internet Applications",
        "Automated Responsive Internet Actions"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is not a principle of the WCAG?",
      "answer": "Dependable",
      "badAnswers": ["Perceivable", "Operable", "Understandable"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of these color contrast ratios defines the minimum WCAG 2.1 Level AA requirement for normal text?",
      "answer": "4.5:1",
      "badAnswers": ["3:1", "7:1", "2:1"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following elements is inherently focusable, meaning it can receive focus without a 'tabindex' attribute?",
      "answer": "<a href='...'>",
      "badAnswers": ["<div>", "<span>", "<p>"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the purpose of the 'lang' attribute in an HTML page?",
      "answer": "To indicate the language of the page content",
      "badAnswers": [
        "To specify the scripting language",
        "To define the character set",
        "To declare a language pack"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which guideline ensures that content is accessible by keyboard as well as by mouse?",
      "answer": "Keyboard Accessible",
      "badAnswers": [
        "Mouse Independence",
        "Device Independence",
        "Operable Controls"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the role of 'skip navigation' links in web accessibility?",
      "answer": "To skip over primary navigation to the main content",
      "badAnswers": [
        "To provide shortcuts to different sections of the website",
        "To help users skip unwanted sections like advertisements",
        "To bypass broken links in the navigation"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of these tools can help in checking the accessibility of a website?",
      "answer": "Google Lighthouse",
      "badAnswers": ["W3C Validator", "CSS Validator", "JavaScript Console"]
    }
  ]
}
